Finding Aid for the Grantland Rice Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Newspaper clippings of poems, articles, and columns by Grantland Rice
  - Index of all poems, articles, and columns by Grantland Rice
    - The Annual Fever (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - The Annual Hip-Hip (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - The Annual Spring Reveille (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - The Annual Stymie (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Another Autumn Sport (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Another 'Ballad of East and West' (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Another Gridiron (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Another 'Hesperus' Wreck (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Another Lap (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Another 'Midsummer Night's Dream' (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Another One (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Another Popular Song (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Another Proclamation (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Another Spring (Box 7, Folder 32, Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Another Winter Sport (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Another Year 4-19, 25 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - The Answer 4-20, 28; 5-3, 14, 15, 27 (Box 6, Folder 31, Box 7, Folder 39)
    - The Answer Being (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Answering a Query (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - The Antidote (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - The Anvil Chorus (Box 6, Folder 21, Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Anything Else, Please (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - An Appeal to the Press (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Applause (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Approving Mr. Markham's 'Hoe' Pome (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - April (Box 5, Folder 5, Box 7, Folder 11)
    - An April Defi (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - April--10 Years Ago (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - The Arch-Fiend of the Ages (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Are You Set, Professor? (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Armed--A Pretty Fair Horse (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Armistice Day (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Army and Navy (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - The Army and the Navy (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Around the Circuit (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Around the Corner (Box 5, Folder 27, Box 6, Folder 42)
    - An Artistic Effort (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - As an Old Year Wanes (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - As "Big Bill" Would See It (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - As Brave a Dream (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - As Christmas Comes (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - As Dreams Go (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - As for Ancient Mottos (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - As for April (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - As, for Instance (Box 5, Folder 27, Box 7, Folder 36)
    - As for July 1st (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - As for 1928 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - As for Putting (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - As for Renaming the Yanks (Box 5, Folder 15, Box 6, Folder 1)
    - As for Suffrage 5-12 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - As for the Red Sox (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - As for Winter Sport (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - As for World Champions (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - As Gipp Looks Down (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - As It Was--And Shall Be (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - As It Was in the Beginning (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - As It Was--Is--And Will Be (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - As Kipling Would See It (Box 4, Folder 3, Box 5, Folder 21)
    - As Sung by the Evans Faction (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - As the Fan Sees It (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - As the Fan Would Have Penned It (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - As the Fever Returns (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - As the Game 'Breaks' (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - As the Game Goes (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - As the Parade Goes By (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - As the Years Move (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - As They Recite It in Boston Just Now (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - As They Send It Out (Box 4, Folder 7, Box 5, Folder 16)
    - As to Courage (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - As to Thanks and Such (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - As Warbled by C. Mack (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - As We Grow Older (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Asking a Question (Box 7, Folder 32, 44)
    - Asking a When (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Asking a Which (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Asking a Why (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Asleep in the Night (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - An Associated Press Lyric (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - At Dusk in Camp (Box 6, Folder 5, 6)
    - At Last (Box 5, Folder 10, 13)
    - At League Park Friday (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - At the Call to Arms (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - At the Count of Nine (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - At the Day's End (Box 4, Folder 18, Box 5, Folder 12)
    - At the End (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - At the End of the Game (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - At the End of the Line (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - At the End of the Way (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - At the Game's End (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - At the Gray Threshold 4-27 (Box 5, Folder 5, Box 6, Folder 51)
    - At the Hermitage (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - At the Journey's End (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - At the Morning Gate (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - At the Olympiad (Box 4, Folder 22, Box 5, Folder 12)
    - At the Season's End 4-7 (Box 5, Folder 12, Box 8, Folder 6)
    - At the Tavemof Life (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - At the Winter Gate (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - At Twilight (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Au Revoir! (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - August (Box 4, Folder 28, Box 5, Folder 5)
    - August in Arcady (Box 4, Folder 22, 23)
    - August Literature (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Autumn (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Autumn Golf (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - The Autumn Jubilee (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Autumn Song (Box 4, Folder 19, 21)
    - The Autumn War Cry (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Autumnal Visions (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Autumn's Threnody (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - The Average (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Aviation and Versification (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - The Awakening (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Awarding Comfort (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Babe Ruth (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Babe Ruth Speaks (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - The "Babe" Speaks (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - The Bachelor's Leap-Year Conundrum (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Back Again (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Back at It (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Back from the Fight (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Back Home (Box 4, Folder 20, Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Back Home Again (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Back of the Scenes (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Back to Belmont (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Back to Bingen (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Back to Morning (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Back to the Off-Trail (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Back Yonder (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Ballad of Brave Life (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - A Ballad of the Batty Brigade (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Ballad of the Day Before (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Ballade of a New Complaint (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Ballade of a Plea (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Ballade of a Reply (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Ballade of Batting Eyes (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Ballade of Battle Lines (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Ballade of Beaten Brave (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Ballade of Bruisers (Box 7, Folder 16, Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Ballade of Bum Golfers (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Ballade of Fighting Men (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Ballade of Golfers (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Ballade of July First (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Ballade of Non-Complaint (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Ballade of Remembrance (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Ballade of the Biggest Bug (Box 4, Folder 21, Box 6, Folder 31)
    - A Ballade of the Day (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Ballade of the Fair Sex (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Ballade of the Fan (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Ballade of the Fan's Rejoinder (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Ballade of the February Phenoms (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - The Ballade of the Game Fish (Box 6, Folder 25, 36, Box 7, Folder 3, 8)
    - Ballade of the Gamefish (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Ballade of the Game's Break (Box 5, Folder 13, 15)
    - Ballade of the Greatest Leader (Box 5, Folder 13, Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Ballade of the Master Moundsman (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Ballade of the Missing (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Ballade of the Nashville Bug (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Ballade of 'The New Leaf (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Ballade of the Simple Life (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Ballade of the T.R. Twins (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Ballade of the True Brave (Box 4, Folder 20, Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Ballade of the Universal Spiel (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Ballade of the White Man's Burden (Box 5, Folder 10, Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Ballads for the Batty Brigade (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Ballads of Bad Babies (Box 4, Folder 8, Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Ballads of the Winter League (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - A Balldom Lullaby (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Balldom's Nursery Ballads (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - The Bard's Complaint (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - The Bard's Revery (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Base Camp No. 1 Speaks (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - "Baseball, as she is writ ..." (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Baseball Futurity (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - The Baseball Girl (Box 4, Folder 7, Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Baseball in Rome (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - The Baseball Writer's Dream (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - 'Batter Up!' (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - The Battle Cry (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Battle Day (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - The Battle of St. Louis (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - The Battle of the Epoch (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - A Battle of the Jungle Championship (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - The Battle of the Sexes (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Battle Song of the Napoleons (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - The Beaten Candidate's Invictus (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Behind the Veil (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - The Bells across the Snow (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Bermuda Golf Problems (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Beyond All Things (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Beyond the Barrier (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Beyond the Beaten Track (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Beyond the Beyond (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Beyond the Finish (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Beyond the Fog (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Beyond the Game (Box 5, Folder 13, Box 6, Folder 11, 30)
    - Beyond the Mist (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Beyond the Twilight (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Beyond the Walls (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Beyond the Years (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Beyond the Snow Line (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Beyond Us (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - The Big Date (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - The Big Game (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - The Big Guns Speak (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Big Fortune is Spent for Players (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - The Big If of Racing (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Big Ifs of History (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - The Big League and the Bush (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - The Big Three (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - The Big Three down the Field (Box 6, Folder 4, Box 7, Folder 40)
    - The Big Three of History (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - The Big Three Try It Out (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - The Big Train (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - The Bigger Hit (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Bill Armour's Dream (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - The Bill Collector's Plaint (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Bill Shakespeare's Vision (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Bill Was a Batter (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - "The birds are glad" (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - "The birds still sing" (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - The Bivouac of May the First (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - The Bivouac of Our Dead Pennant Hopes (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - The Bivouac of the Dope (Box 5, Folder 14, Box 6, Folder 31)
    - The Blighted (Box 5, Folder 28, Box 6, Folder 1)
    - The Blighted City (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Blue Days and Fair (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - The Blue Jubilee (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Blue or Green? (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - A Blue Rejoinder (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - The Blue Sky Artist (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Boarder's Riddles (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Bobby Jones (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Booming the Program (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - A Boston War Song (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - A Bow to the Infantry (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Bowing to Buck (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - The Box Score's Story (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Boy Scout Reverie in a City Street (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Boyland (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Branding the Entry (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Brave Life (Box 4, Folder 14, Box 7, Folder 39)
    - The Break of the Game (Box 5, Folder 13, Box 7, Folder 21)
    - The Bright Side of It (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Broadway Column (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Broken Blossoms (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - The Bromide Champ (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - A Brooding Thought (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Budding Phenoms (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Budding Phenoms of the Game (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - The Buggy Whip (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - The Bug's Viewpoint (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - The Building of the Pyramids (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Bunged up on the Nine (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Bunged up on the Spine (Box 4, Folder 3, Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Bungling on the Nine (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Bunkered (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Der Burghouse Master (Box 4, Folder 8, Box 5, Folder 21)
    - The Buried Talent (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - The Bush League Speaks Again (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - The Bush Leaguer's Dream (Box 4, Folder 14, 20)
    - The Bush to the Big League (Box 7, Folder 38, Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Busy ,Getting Ready' (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Buying an Automobile (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - By an Autumn Tree (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - By Way of Chiding (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - By Way of Interval (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - By Way of Memory (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - By Way of Sound Advice (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - A Byronic Appeal (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - The Caddie's Story (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - The Cagey Duffer Speaks (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - The Call Sternal (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - The Call for Pat Moran (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - The Call of our Forces (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - The Call of the Age (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - The Call of the Ancient Green (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - The Call of the Ancient Spring (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - The Call of the Back Trail (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - The Call of the Blue Grass Country (Box 5, Folder 4, 21)
    - The Call of the Curfew (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - The Call of the Eagle (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - The Call of the Fan (Box 6, Folder 1, Box 7, Folder 41)
    - The Call of the Road (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - The Call of the Sun (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - The Call of the Tall and Uncut 5-3A i (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - The Call of the Wild (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - The Call to Arms (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Callahan vs Callahan (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Campus Echoes (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Can Spring Be Far Behind? (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - The Canadian (Box 7, Folder 36, 43)
    - The Cap and Bells (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Carlisle's Defiance (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Carrying On (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Casey in the Box (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Casey Up-to-Date (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Casey's Finish Comes in Football Game (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Casey's Revenge (Box 4, Folder 2, Box 7, Folder 24)
    - The Cause Eternal (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - The Challenging Cry (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - The Champion (Box 5, Folder 6, 28, Box 6, Folder 41, 67)
    - A Champion You May Know About (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - The Champions (Box 6, Folder 5, 6)
    - Champions' Chances for 1934 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Chance for Larry to Cinch Pennant (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Chance to Jennings (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - A Change for the Better (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - A Change in Heroes (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - The Chant of the Second Division Bug (Box 5, Folder 8, Box 7, Folder 39)
    - The Charge (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - The Charge of the Tip Brigade (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Charon Calls Again (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Charley Van Loan (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Chasing Slang (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - A Ch'rup Ditty (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Cheer Up, for Just Suppose (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Cheer Up! or, Have Your Forgotten? (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Cheer Up, North (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - A Cheer-Up Smear (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Cheering, Music and the Player (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - The Chief (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Childhood (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - A Christmas Confession (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - A Christmas Ditty (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Christmas Eve (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - A Christmas Eve Dream (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Christmas Eve in Camp (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Christmas in Sportland (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Christmas in Vagabondia (Box 5, Folder 4, 14)
    - Christmas 1943
    - A Christmas of the Long Ago (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Christmas on the Off-Trail (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - A Christmas Plea (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - A Christmas Prayer (Box 5, Folder 13, 23)
    - A Christmas Revery (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Christmas Sporting Carols (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - The Cinch Tip (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Circus Day (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - The City of Saltillo (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Clan to Clan (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - The Classic Headline (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - The Clearest Vision (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Clem McCarthy (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Cleveland's Greatest Sons (Box 4, Folder 3, Box 5)
    - The Climax of Fan Joy (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Close Call (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - The Closing Act (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - The Club Owner's Dream (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - The Coach's Dream (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - The Coach's Happy Dream (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Coblenz on the Rhine (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Col. Abe Attell's Rejoinder (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Collaborated (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Collegiate Preparation (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Collegiate Remembrances (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - The 'Come Back' (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Come On, June (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Come On, Team (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Comes One with a Song (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - The Coming Box core (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - The Coming Melody (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Coming On (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - A Commencement Medley (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Commercializing Football (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Commodore War Song (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Commodores in Form (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Compensation (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Competitive Temperament (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Complaint from a Bard (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Comradeship (Box 4, Folder 24, Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Concerning a Certain Sporting Philosophy (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Concerning a Major Sport (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Concerning a New Baseball Season (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Concerning a Recent Political Upset (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Concerning Another Year (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Concerning Certain Maxims (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Concerning E. Arcaro (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Concerning J. Demaret's Apparel (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Concerning Johnson's Speed (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Concerning Old Doc Diogenes (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Concerning the Anvil Chorus (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Concerning the Dodgers (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Concerning the Late Hack Wilson (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Concerning the Lorimer Episode (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Concerning Two Pals (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - A Confession (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Connie and Lonnie and Matt (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - The Conquered (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - The Conqueror (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Consolation (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Contentment (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - The Contrast (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - The Conundrum of the Golf Shops (Box 5, Folder 14, Box 7, Folder 12)
    - The Cost Repaid (Box 4, Folder 1, Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Could Anything Be Finer? (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - The Courtship of a Son of Swat (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Count Fleet (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - The Cotton-Wood Trail (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Cracking under the Strain (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Crafty Chesbro (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - The Creed of Compensation (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - A Crimson Dream (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - The Cry of the Winds (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - The Cub Fan's Dream (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Cubs Cop the Opener (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Cumberland's Callin'--Come Home (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Cy Is Still in the Game (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - The Daily Problem 4-22, 24 The Daily Spiel 4-25 Danny Deevered (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - 'The Dawn of a New Era (Box 4, Folder 1, Box 5, Folder 16)
    - The Day After (Box 6, Folder 14, 15)
    - The Day Before (Box 6, Folder 35, 59)
    - A Day in the Bleachers (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - The Day of Real Sport (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - The Day's News (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - 'De Profundis' (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - The Deadliest Thing in the World (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - De-Brutalized Football (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - "Deep in the dusk" (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Defeated (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Dempsey's Luck (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Dempsey's Soliloquy 6-46, 51 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Denton (Cy) Young (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - A Deserved Rest (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Diamond Gossip from Master Pens (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - The Diet Debate (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - The Difference (Box 4, Folder 20, Box 6, Folder 66, Box 7, Folder 16, 21)
    - A Difference in Taste (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Diogenes and His 'Search Warrant' (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Diogenes and the Sporting Game (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Dirge of the Winter League (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Disappointed (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - The Discoverer Incarnate (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - The Disturber (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Dixie--My Dixie (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Dixie Parodies (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Do We Say Something? (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - The Dodger Fan (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Dodger Ornithology (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - The Dodgers and the Cardinals (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - A Doggerel of the Gamp (Box 4, Folder 3, Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Donald the Dub (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Donlin's Return (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Donlin's Soliloquy (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Dooin's Rejoinder (Box 5, Folder 11, 15)
    - The Dope (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Dope and the Game (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Dope on the Derby's Eve (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - The Dopist Dictionary (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Down Dreamway (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Down on the Field (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Down the Road (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - The Down Under (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Down Where the Cotton Blossoms Grow (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Down Where the South Begins (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - The Downfall (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Downstream (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - A Dream (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - A Dream and a Nightmare (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - The Dream City (Box 4, Folder 13, Box 5, Folder 8, 11, Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Dream Ghosts (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - A Dream of a Napland Fan (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - A Dream in the Shadows (Box 4, Folder 12, Box 5, Folder 19)
    - A Dream of Far-Off Lands (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - A Dream of September (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - A Dream of Thanksgiving (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - A Dream of the Day (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - A Dream of the Golden Past (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - A Dream of the Sea (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - (The) Dream Vagabonds (Box 5, Folder 8, Box 6, Folder 36)
    - (The) Dreamers (Box 4, Folder 18, Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Driftwood (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - The Drive (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - The Dry Game (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Ducking a Query (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - The Duffer Addresses a Golfing Adviser (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - The Duffer and the Moon (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - The Duffer Articulates (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - The Duffer Exclaims Again (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - The Duffer Interjects (Box 5, Folder 29, Box 6, Folder 2, 45)
    - The Duffer Reflects (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - The Duffer Remarks (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - The Duffer Speaks (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - The Duffer Speaks Again (Box 8, Folder 2, 18)
    - The Duffer--The Iron Man of Sport (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - The Duffer to the Pro (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - A Duffer's Ambition (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - The Duffer's April Song (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - The Duffer's Bitter Squawk (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - The Duffer's Christmas Dream (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - The Duffer's Dirge (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - The Duffer's Confession (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - The Duffer's Invictus (Box 5, Folder 29, Box 8, Folder 18, 21)
    - The Duffer's Lament (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - The Duffer's Lot (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - The Duffer's Nightmare (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - The Duffer's Rebuttal (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - The Duffer's Revision (Box 5, Folder 29, Box 6, Folder 51, 54)
    - The Duffer's Revery (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - The Duffer's Song of Cheer (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - The Duffer's Spring (Box 7, Folder 14)